SERGE CHURKIN

C

289-501-7013

 $oxed{oxed}$

sergechurkin@gmail.com



/sergechurkin/



sergechurkin-ca



www.serge-web.com



Toronto, ON

CORE COMPETENCIES

Technical Skills:

- HTML5 / SCSS
- Responsive design
- JavaScript
- API
- Github and Collaboration
- iQuery
- React and Firebase
- Node.js and Express

Additional Skills:

- Leadership
- Complex problem solving
- Project Management
- Customer service
- Communication, Presentations and Public Speaking

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology, Toronto | 2020

- Web Development Immersive Certificate (Bootcamp)
- Accelerated Javascript
- Introduction to Web Development

Niagara College Canada, Niagara Falls, ON | 2016 - 2018

- International Business
 Management
- Tourism and Hospitality Management

PROFILE SUMMARY

Front End Web Developer who is passionate about building accessible and responsive web applications. I combine my background in large scale operations management and driving excellent customer care with my technical skillset to create user-friendly web experiences.

PROJECTS

Recipe Generator - JavaScript, API, jQuery, UX Design | <u>View Live</u>
Poll It Together - React, Firebase, Github, Collaboration | <u>View Live</u>
Tour Agency Inventory - React, Firebase | <u>View Live</u>
Country Quiz - JavaScript, UX Design, SCSS | <u>View Live</u>

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Fallsview Group Group of Hotels Niagara Falls, ON Night Audit Supervisor May 2018 - January 2020

- Improved processing of daily financial and balancing reports from 5 to 1.5 hrs
- Maximized revenue and ensured 101% hotel occupancy of property with 200 rooms by monitoring reservations and updating rates
- Supervised and trained 2 auditors, tought shortcuts and depths of hotel booking system

Night Auditor Aug 2016 - May 2018

- Reconciled, audited and balanced accounts, prepared revenue reports in property with 600 rooms
- Checked in guests, answered the calls and instant messages and ensured high standard of service

TEZ TOUR Thailand Phuket, Thailand Regional Manager Feb 2015 - Feb 2016

- Oversaw inbound tourism operations in Phuket region, managed the team of 100 employees
- Developed strategies to implement sales targets and increased regional revenue by 20%
- Successfully maintained industry leadership image of the company among 200 local partner hotels and 25 tour suppliers

Quality Control Manager Jul 2013 - Jan 2015

- Improved the quality of service and advanced evaluation system in Phuket region with 200 daily arrivals
- Developed and updated administrative policies and guidelines to maintain high quality of operations
- Obtained and tracked guest's feedback, resolved complaints and achieved satisfaction